Release 7		2005-07-26
  Fixed many crash bugs.
  Removed the need to have MSVCR71.dll.
  Added DSP disassembler.
  Vastly improved graphics emulation, using pixel shaders.
  Changed window title to show game name instead of file name. (GCMs only.)
  Added an option to turn debug logging off and on. It is off by default.
  Added an option to disable the syscall instruction, enabling Freeloader and
    Action Replay.